Protect the Bloodline
Underworld: Blood Wars is a fantasy, action,
thriller film directed by Anna Foerster.
Vampire death dealer Selene fends off brutal attacks from both the
Lycan clan and the Vampire faction that betrayed her.
With her only allies, David and his father Thomas, she must stop the eternal war between
Lycans and Vampires, even if it means she has to make the ultimate sacrifice.
Selene, played by Kate Beckinsale.
David, played by Theo James.
Marius, played by Tobias Menzies.
Semira, played by Lara Pulver.
Varga, played by Bradley James.
Vidar, played by Peter Andersson.
Underworld: Blood Wars is a 2016 action horror film directed by Anna Foerster from a
screenplay by Cory Goodman, based on a story by Kyle Ward and Goodman.
It is the sequel to Underworld: Awakening (2012) and the fifth and
final installment in the Underworld film series.
The film stars Kate Beckinsale, Theo James, Lara
Pulver, James Faulkner, and Charles Dance.
Principal photography began in October 2015 in Prague, Czech Republic.
Underworld: Blood Wars was released in select countries on November 24,
2016, and was released in the United States on January 6, 2017.
The film was panned by critics and grossed $81.1 million worldwide against a production
budget of $35 million, making it the lowest-grossing film in the franchise.
The film explores themes of martial arts, sword, vampire, hybrid, ambition.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.